broadjam.com 2019-04-22

# Privacy Policy | Broadjam Legal

* ******GENERAL**

This Privacy Policy explains the policy of Broadjam Inc. regarding the privacy of information supplied by users or collected by us from users of the site. As part of the normal operation of the site, we collect information about you. This Privacy Policy describes generally the information we collect about you and how this information is used. 

#### Information Collection and Use

We will endeavor to respect your privacy and will only use your personal information for reasonable business purposes. We will not sell or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this Privacy Policy.

#### Information You Provide

When you register an account with Broadjam, we collect the following personal information: first name, last name, artist name, date of birth, gender, email address, physical address, and telephone number. We also collect information about you when you subscribe to Broadjam's various services, when you visit Broadjam's pages or the pages of certain Broadjam partners, and when you enter promotions or sweepstakes. Broadjam may combine information about you that we have with information we obtain from business partners or other companies.   
We use your email address to uniquely identify you to allow you access to your account. We also use your email address to send you emailed newsletters and to inform you of sales and special offers. If you don't want to receive these types of emails from us, you may opt-out. In order to establish a more personalized relationship with you, we may also use your personal information to determine what services you truly value.

#### Correcting/Updating Personal Information

You will be able to edit certain elements of your personal information in the "profile" section of our site. Any changes you make are automatically saved.

#### Choices for Information

If you no longer wish to receive Broadjam's emailed newsletters or information about sales and special offers, you may opt-out of receiving these communications by clicking "Unsubscribe" at the bottom of a newsletter. You may also change your emailed newsletter preferences in the "MY ACCOUNT" section of our site.

#### Third-Party Relationships

We will not, without your consent, sell our customer e-mail address list to third parties. When you choose to access certain Broadjam partners' sites through links on Broadjam.com, Broadjam may ask you for specific permission to forward your personal information to such partners for purposes of pre-populating their online sign-up forms. Please be aware that Broadjam is not responsible for the information practices of these third-party sites. For more information, please see the Links section below.

#### Log Files

Our log files automatically store IP addresses. We use IP addresses to administer the site and gather broad information about our customers. We also store IP addresses with invoices for security reasons. We keep this information for our internal use only.

#### Security

When you submit personal information on this site, we will endeavor to protect your information both online and offline. We use Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encryption to protect your payment information.   
We protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure once we receive it through a variety of procedures. Only employees of Broadjam have access to such personal information, and they are kept up-to-date on our security procedures and privacy policy. We have implemented security systems that we believe prevent most people from accessing your personal information through our site. People who try and bypass security systems, or "Hackers", are often very skilled at breaking through security systems though and therefore we can make no guarantee that your information is 100% safe.

#### Cookies

If you have the settings on your browser set accordingly, we will use "cookies" to track some of your information in order to customize our site for you. "Cookies" are text files that we'll place on the hard drive of your computer in order to remember your password, preferences, etc. Allowing us to place a "cookie" on your hard drive does not admit us to the remainder of your computer and "cookies" have purportedly been designed by Microsoft so that Broadjam Inc. will be the only entity that can read the "cookie" we place on your hard drive. You have the option to set your web browser to reject cookies and if you do so some features of our site will not work and therefore some of the personalized options will be eliminated. You should check the documentation of your browser to learn how to disable "cookies."

#### Links

It is important to note that the Broadjam Inc. site contains links to other sites, and that those sites may not follow the same privacy policies as Broadjam Inc. For instance, if you click on an advertisement on the Broadjam Inc. site, you may be taken away from Broadjam Inc. to an entirely different site. These links can also be from advertisers, content providers and/or partners who may use Broadjam Inc.'s logo and/or style as a result of a co-branding agreement yet they may still not follow the same privacy policies as Broadjam Inc.   
Some promotions, contests and sweepstakes appearing on the Broadjam Inc. site may be sponsored or co-sponsored by other companies. These companies may also choose to collect personal information from you. Broadjam Inc. cannot control the privacy policies of these outside sponsors, and if you do not want your information collected by these sponsors, you should not participate in the promotion, contest or sweepstakes.

#### Notification of Changes

Broadjam reserves the right, at any time and from time to time, to update, revise, supplement and to otherwise modify this Privacy Policy. Such updates, revisions, supplements and modifications will be effective immediately and incorporated into this Privacy Policy upon notice thereof, which may be given by any reasonable means including by posting to the site. Your continued use of the site following such notice will be deemed to conclusively indicate your acceptance of any and all such changes.

#### Legal Disclaimer

Notwithstanding anything to the contrary contained herein, Broadjam Inc. reserves the right to disclose user information when required by law, or if we have reason to believe that someone is causing injury to or interference with our rights or property, or the rights and property of others.   
By using this site, you signify your assent to Broadjam Inc.'s privacy policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our site.   
If you are unclear about any of the above stated policies or just have a question for us, please contact us at [customerservice@broadjam.com](mailto:customerservice@broadjam.com).

back to top
